module.exports = [
  { question: `In what country would you find the Yellow River?`, answer: 'China' },
  { question: `Formerly known as Bedloe's Island, what is the current name of the island where the Statue of Liberty is located?`, answer: 'Liberty Island' },
  { question: `Sardinia, the second largest island in the Mediterranean Sea, is an autonomous region of what country?`, answer: 'Italy' },
  { question: `Beirut is the capital and largest city of what country?`, answer: 'Lebanon' },
  { question: `The Grand Canyon is located in which U.S. state?`, answer: 'Arizona' },
  { question: `Located in Northwestern Turkey, which strait separates Europe and Asia?`, answer: 'Bosphorus Strait' },
  { question: `South Africa completely surrounds which other African nation?`, answer: 'Lesotho' },
  { question: `Europe is separated from Asia by which mountain range?`, answer: 'Ural Mountains' },
  { question: `What is the largest country in North America?`, answer: 'Canada' },
  { question: `Which of the great lakes does not share a border with Canada?`, answer: 'Lake Michigan' },
  { question: `What is the national language of India?`, answer: 'Hindi' },
  { question: `What is the largest island in the Caribbean Sea?`, answer: 'Cuba' },
  { question: `Which city in the United States is known as the "Windy City"?`, answer: 'Chicago' },
  { question: `What city is the capital of China?`, answer: 'Beijing' },
  { question: `What city is the capital of Canada?`, answer: 'Ottawa' }
]
